<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tom Bush | Data Science/SEO</title>
    <link>https://tomfbush.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Tom Bush | Data Science/SEO</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2020 13:05:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tomfbush.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to remove duplicate rows in SQL (works with Postgres)</title>
      <link>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/how-to-remove-duplicate-rows-in-sql-works-with-postgres/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2020 13:05:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/how-to-remove-duplicate-rows-in-sql-works-with-postgres/</guid>
      <description>Note to self more than anything, this snippet was handy for to remove duplicate rows in SQL, that crept into a Postgres database as a result of a dodgy join.
There are probably more than a couple of ways of doing this but the best example I came up with after reading around is:
DELETE FROM table_name WHERE ctid NOT IN ( SELECT min(ctid) FROM table_name GROUP BY field1, field2); The reason this works revolves around the ctid field.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Review Checklist App</title>
      <link>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/weekly-review-checklist-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2017 20:15:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/weekly-review-checklist-app/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been toying with the idea of creating an app that helps with a weekly review for a while. I first came across the idea when reading about Getting Things Done and the massive list of &amp;lsquo;triggers&amp;rsquo; that comes with that. To be honest I found it a bit daunting and didn&amp;rsquo;t need to check all those things every week. So, in my own simple, trivial way I&amp;rsquo;ve written what is essentially just a web page with a list on it, except that the list updates a progress bar and nicely removes things from focus when they are complete.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Insert Key (or equivalent) on Ubuntu using a Mac keyboard</title>
      <link>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/insert-key-equivalent-ubuntu-using-mac-keyboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2016 12:29:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/insert-key-equivalent-ubuntu-using-mac-keyboard/</guid>
      <description>Pretty niche audience for this one, but posting it for my own benefit as much as anything. Thanks to the original link at Ubuntu Forums for the following hints:
[fn] + [return] = Insert [fn] + [UPARROW] = Pg Up [fn] + [DOWNARROW]= Pg Down  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ways To Save Money</title>
      <link>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/ways-to-save-money/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 May 2015 18:14:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/ways-to-save-money/</guid>
      <description>Checklist for saving money This is a page all about various methods of saving some cash! I add ideas here when I come up with them, so this is definitely a work in progress. If you have any ways to save money that I haven&amp;rsquo;t added here then please leave a note in the comments! [caption id=&amp;ldquo;attachment_522&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;ldquo;aligncenter&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;ldquo;225&amp;rdquo;]There are loads of ways to save money and anyone can start[/caption]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easy Sumif in R Using The Aggregate Function</title>
      <link>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/sumif-in-r-like-excel-aggregate/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2015 20:47:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/sumif-in-r-like-excel-aggregate/</guid>
      <description>This is a really simple (i.e. probably even the most basic possible) example of using the built in aggregate() function in R, basically a sumif in R. Given a set of data where column a is the values and column b contains the data by which you wish to group (in this example categorical data with values of a or b):
&amp;gt; data a b 1 0 a 2 0 a 3 1 b 4 2 a 5 2 b 6 2 a 7 3 b 8 4 b 9 7 b The aggregate function as I have used it below takes the following arguments &amp;ndash; data$a is the column we are applying a function to; by = refers to a list of names and references to aggregate things by (in this case just one column, so the list has a single element); finally the function we are using here is the built in sum (but this could be a function of your own making, or a mean, or whatever):</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 10 HTML Beginner Resources</title>
      <link>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/html-beginner-resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2015 18:35:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/html-beginner-resources/</guid>
      <description>Beginning with HTML Over the past few weeks I&amp;rsquo;ve noticed a few people have been asking me if I had any tips for the best HTML beginner resources. This is something that comes up for myself once in while when needing some bit of HTML reference that I have forgotten through under-use. In order to kill two (three?) birds with one stone I thought I would make a list for myself&amp;ndash;in the form of a post&amp;ndash;that I could share with those people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 Apps To Improve Samsung Galaxy S4 Battery Life</title>
      <link>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/3-apps-will-increase-samsung-galaxy-s4-battery-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2015 09:10:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/3-apps-will-increase-samsung-galaxy-s4-battery-life/</guid>
      <description>Improving the Samsung Galaxy S4 Battery Life What follows is a short intro to 3 apps that in my experience have improved my SGS4 battery life &amp;ndash; your mileage may vary and I can&amp;rsquo;t be to blame for any damage caused! That said, I don&amp;rsquo;t think any of these should render your phone unusable :)
CPU Tuner This is the daddy of all battery saving apps, and works best when your phone is rooted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pretty print JSON in Python (snippet)</title>
      <link>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/pretty-print-json-python-snippet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2015 09:52:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/pretty-print-json-python-snippet/</guid>
      <description>The below depends on the json Python module to &amp;lsquo;pretty print&amp;rsquo; JSON output in Python. I found this useful when trying to write my script to remove unused Todoist labels.
import json # This function saves time printing JSON nicely def pj(str): print(json.dumps(json.loads(str.content), indent=4)) return pj(thing_containing_raw_json_here) Note that in my case this was contingent on having used the requests module in the following fashion to already make sure the format is a bit jsonified, if I understand the .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Todoist: Remove unused labels</title>
      <link>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/remove-unused-todoist-labels/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2015 19:18:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/remove-unused-todoist-labels/</guid>
      <description>Want to remove your unused labels/tags from Todoist in bulk? The various GUIs will have you do this one at a time but I have written a small, not very efficient Python script that will do this for you. Here&amp;rsquo;s how it works:
 You need to provide your API token (Which you can find in Todoist settings) in a file called token.txt Then download or copy the script from my Todoist Remove Unused Tags GitHub repository Just run this using Python and it should work fine  Please bear in mind I&amp;rsquo;ve only tested this on my setup so it could go wrong, although it&amp;rsquo;s highly unlikely.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week Commencing Excel Formula</title>
      <link>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/week-commencing-excel/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2014 20:11:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/week-commencing-excel/</guid>
      <description>A lot of the data we use is on a daily basis. This is great for more granular insight and for pacing media spend etc. Sometimes however you want to bundle it all up into nice, weekly buckets (often based on &amp;lsquo;week commencing&amp;rsquo;) so that you can look at how weeks affect the sales pattern over the month, for example. This might be harder to see based on daily data. If you need to calculate the week commencing date in Excel (i.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>15 Best Holiday Tips Beyond The Packing List</title>
      <link>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/best-holiday-tips/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2014 18:49:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/best-holiday-tips/</guid>
      <description>We recently went on a holiday to New York. On the last day we stopped in at the Gasoline Alley coffee company and took 15 mins to write down some of the things that had helped it go smoothly. Here are our 15 best holiday tips (and here we’re talking about things you can do to help enjoy your holiday, not the best ways to buy a holiday or a packing list).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tom Bush wikipedia</title>
      <link>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/tom-bush-wikipedia/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2014 22:41:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/tom-bush-wikipedia/</guid>
      <description>The Tom Bush Wikipedia Test This is just a test to see what happens when I create a page supposed to rank around searches for &amp;ldquo;tom bush wikipedia&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WinSXS cleanup: how to remove GB of files in the WinSXS folder</title>
      <link>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/winsxs-cleanup-get-rid-gb-files-winsxs-folder/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2014 22:18:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/winsxs-cleanup-get-rid-gb-files-winsxs-folder/</guid>
      <description>This post is a quick one on WinSXS cleanup, and it works (for me). None of the instructions I found online helped me, including the KB2852386 fix on Windows update. Try this:
 Go to C:\Windows\system32 Right click on cleanmgr.exe and Run As Administrator Now, the relevant &amp;ldquo;Windows Update Cleanup&amp;rdquo; option and another for cleaning up Service Pack backups should appear. Tick them both Proceed!  For me this worked a treat for WinSXS cleanup.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>bbLean flickering with Chrome/Firefox/other: FIX</title>
      <link>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/bblean-flickering-chrome-firefox-titlebar/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2014 21:09:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/bblean-flickering-chrome-firefox-titlebar/</guid>
      <description>I just loaded up bbLean as a way of speeding up my old Win7 laptop, only to discover that Google Chrome (the app I use the most) was flickering really badly because it has its own skin, and bbLean was trying to apply its own titlebar too. I would have just commented on Nimret&amp;rsquo;s blog to say thanks, but it seems that comments are turned off. I decided to post thanks and the method here instead (but you can read the original here).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Biddable Media: Will All Advertising One Day Be Biddable?</title>
      <link>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/biddable-media-will-advertising-space-one-day-biddable/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2014 17:22:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/biddable-media-will-advertising-space-one-day-biddable/</guid>
      <description>Introduction to biddable media Behind Google&amp;rsquo;s huge advertising revenue, behind those annoying banners you see all over the web, behind the skippable ads before YouTube videos is the phenomenon of real-time bidding (RTB). This is a method of buying advertising space that, rather than arranging it in advance via a tenancy or reservation buy (i.e. money up front at an agreed price), relies on an auction taking place usually at lightning speed, between interested parties.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/privacy-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2013 13:46:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/privacy-policy/</guid>
      <description>Privacy Policy for tombush.co.uk As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit the site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout the site. I also use third party advertisements to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on the site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit the site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Convert dates to text in Excel: days, months, times and more</title>
      <link>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/convert-dates-text-excel-days-months-times/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2013 13:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/convert-dates-text-excel-days-months-times/</guid>
      <description>This article will look at ways to convert dates to text in Excel; that means converting dates into day names, hours, months and more. This is a really simple thing to do but it has a number of uses. As an aside, when you work with data on a daily basis, these sorts of Excel tips come up quite often, and whilst its easy enough to go and find the answers on Excel forums, I thought I would start putting them down here in one place so that I remember them myself, but also so that any interested readers can look super smart to their colleagues by knowing this stuff in advance if they don&amp;rsquo;t already.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Best Google Cake Ever (if you liked Insights)</title>
      <link>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/google-cake/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2013 20:43:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/google-cake/</guid>
      <description>[caption id=&amp;ldquo;attachment_342&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;ldquo;alignright&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;ldquo;300&amp;rdquo;]A delicious Google Insights cake[/caption] Google Cakes? There are loads of them. Look closely and you&amp;rsquo;ll even find a cake inspired by Google Analytics. But are you ready for the long, lost, long-tail, best Google cake ever? So I was going through Evernote having a clear out, when I noticed this photo of a Google Insights cake that was made for a competition at work. You may know that Google Insights has been absorbed into Google Trends and had a redesign, so this cake is no longer accurate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LOVEFiLM Buffering Problems? Here&#39;s a workaround!</title>
      <link>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/lovefilm-buffering-problems/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Feb 2013 18:03:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/lovefilm-buffering-problems/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been having LOVEFiLM buffering problems for some time now. This only started when we changed broadband provider, so I&amp;rsquo;m tempted to say that it&amp;rsquo;s Virgin&amp;rsquo;s traffic shaping that is causing the issues. Anyway, I&amp;rsquo;m not writing to moan about that, I don&amp;rsquo;t know exactly what has caused the problem so I&amp;rsquo;m not pointing my finger at anyone. When in full screen mode, I get LOVEFiLM constantly buffering every minute or so, for 2-5 seconds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unhide Multiple Sheets in Excel</title>
      <link>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/unhide-multiple-sheets-in-excel/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jan 2013 10:13:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/unhide-multiple-sheets-in-excel/</guid>
      <description>I recently had a need to unhide multiple sheets in Excel (maybe you call them tabs). Whoever sent me the original file had decided to spread their data out over so many extra sheets that it would have taken almost literally minutes to unhide them all. Naturally, I wasted even more time looking for a way to automate this process. I found two pretty good ways to unhide multiple Excel tabs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WordPress can&#39;t edit category slug</title>
      <link>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/wordpress-cant-edit-category-slug/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2012 19:36:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/wordpress-cant-edit-category-slug/</guid>
      <description>WordPress can&amp;rsquo;t edit category slug? WordPress wouldn&amp;rsquo;t allow me to edit the category slug &amp;ldquo;online-tools-2&amp;rdquo; down to &amp;ldquo;online-tools&amp;rdquo; no matter what I did. Just a quick shout out here to KAVDesign.net who have posted the answer to the problem I was having&amp;hellip; thanks guys. The answer in my case was to delete the tag that already had the same slug (which also leads to asking what I should be using tags and categories for, how they should differ).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4 Wordle Alternatives</title>
      <link>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/4-wordle-alternatives/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Dec 2012 16:10:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/4-wordle-alternatives/</guid>
      <description>What is Wordle? Wordle is a popular online tool that allows you to input a web page, block of text or list of keywords, and have it spit out a graphic known as a word cloud. Wordle does this job pretty well, but something that gets asked at work quite a lot is if there are any Wordle alternatives out there. In addition, Wordle is a little awkward if all you want is an image file at the end of it that you can paste into a presentation for example, without taking screenshots.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sweetcorn alternative</title>
      <link>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/sweetcorn-alternative/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Dec 2012 08:02:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/sweetcorn-alternative/</guid>
      <description>No sweatcorn for me thanks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paste as Plain Text In Any App With Puretext, A Free Portable Windows App</title>
      <link>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/paste-as-plain-text-in-any-app-with-puretext-a-free-portable-windows-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2012 15:40:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/paste-as-plain-text-in-any-app-with-puretext-a-free-portable-windows-app/</guid>
      <description>There are a number of situations that you might want to paste as plain text, i.e. with all formatting removed.
 Lots of copy and pasting from the web results in formatted text. This is fine if you are only pasting into a search box, URL bar or Notepad, but if you are putting this into Evernote, Word, Powerpoint or other rich text aware applications, you don&amp;rsquo;t always want to keep the source formatting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Share YouTube Videos At A Specific Time</title>
      <link>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/how-to-share-youtube-videos-at-a-specific-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2012 15:05:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/how-to-share-youtube-videos-at-a-specific-time/</guid>
      <description>[caption id=&amp;ldquo;attachment_298&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;ldquo;alignright&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;ldquo;300&amp;rdquo;]Sharing a YouTube video at a specific time; although why you would want to skip any of this song is beyond me.[/caption] Okay, so this is nothing new but I still seem to sit through YouTube videos waiting for the one funny bit I&amp;rsquo;ve been told about. Imagine all the time that would be saved in the world if people would just right click on the YouTube video and select &amp;ldquo;Copy Video URL at current time&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Year&#39;s Resolutions 2013: The Year of Aiming Low and Planning Ahead</title>
      <link>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/new-years-resolutions-2013/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2012 18:30:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/new-years-resolutions-2013/</guid>
      <description>Why I can&amp;rsquo;t keep a resolution I make on New Year&amp;rsquo;s Eve Yes yes, I know it&amp;rsquo;s a bit early to be posting my New Year&amp;rsquo;s resolutions for 2013, but every December 31st I decide that I should probably choose to give up something, start doing something, start giving up something or whatever, and I never stick to it because:
 It&amp;rsquo;s not a realistic goal I&amp;rsquo;m clearly not that bothered if I don&amp;rsquo;t want to change it all year round It&amp;rsquo;s usually something vague that allows me to interpret my own rule to the point that the only thing I achieve is outwitting myself  With these points in mind, I have decided to make a list of multiple easy resolutions that will result in an overall net happiness increase, either because they save me money, remove clutter from my head or my room, or may have some kind of other health impact.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Automator for converting PDF to RTF on Mac OSX (download)</title>
      <link>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/automator-for-converting-pdf-to-rtf-on-mac-osx/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Sep 2012 14:04:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/automator-for-converting-pdf-to-rtf-on-mac-osx/</guid>
      <description>I noticed a few people around the web asking how to convert PDFs into RTF (rich text) files, a more useful, accessible format if you are doing a lot of copying and pasting etc. So I&amp;rsquo;ve made a really simple Automator app that will create a RTF on your desktop of any PDF you drop onto it (so I also keep that on my desktop, but it might work from the dock too).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to write a thesis (including how not to write a thesis)</title>
      <link>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/how-to-write-a-thesis/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2012 08:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/how-to-write-a-thesis/</guid>
      <description>Introduction At this stage, I don&amp;rsquo;t know if I&amp;rsquo;m going to pass or fail my MPhil. I&amp;rsquo;ve written around 120,000 words in total over the past half a decade, and submitted 60,000 of those prior to my viva. Of those, 30,000 were utter rubbish and needed rewriting. I&amp;rsquo;m going through that rewriting process now &amp;ndash; things are definitely better, but whether they&amp;rsquo;re good enough I don&amp;rsquo;t know, but I have learnt how to write a thesis with all the wry wisdom of hindsight, and much self-flagellation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Windows Update: Same Updates Over And Over Again (FIX)</title>
      <link>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/windows-update-same-updates-over-and-over-again-fix/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2012 20:25:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/windows-update-same-updates-over-and-over-again-fix/</guid>
      <description>[caption id=&amp;ldquo;attachment_250&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;ldquo;alignright&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;ldquo;199&amp;rdquo;] If Windows Update Failed One More Time My Laptop Would Look Like This (I Don&amp;rsquo;t Know Who That Girl Is Though)[/caption] There was me thinking that the Windows Update mechanism was designed to streamline updates to the operating system, eliminating the need to go to a website to download fixes and patches. Ha ha ha. Without realising it, I&amp;rsquo;ve been repeatedly shutting down to install the same Windows Updates on Vista for the past 2 weeks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sustainably Sourced Pole</title>
      <link>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/sustainably-sourced-pole/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2012 13:12:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/sustainably-sourced-pole/</guid>
      <description>Makes any sandwich taste wonderful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spotify for Android Crashes Fixed</title>
      <link>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/spotify-for-android-crashes-fixed/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jun 2012 22:14:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/spotify-for-android-crashes-fixed/</guid>
      <description>Finally, after months of waiting and an endless stream of complaints from users all over the world, Spotify have updated their Android app and fixed the issues with crashing open opening, crashing when syncing and crashing a few seconds into playing. All these, as you&amp;rsquo;d expect, lead to a pretty poor experience and one that left me feeling a bit ripped off. However, the latest update has a revamped UI that fits nicely with ICS, includes extra features and also DOESN&amp;rsquo;T CRASH.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cooking bacon in the microwave: don&#39;t use the paper towel method</title>
      <link>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/cooking-bacon-in-the-microwave/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2012 17:41:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/cooking-bacon-in-the-microwave/</guid>
      <description>Cooking bacon in the microwave&amp;hellip; the bacon-ground to the story I had been invited to a friend&amp;rsquo;s house. It was just 9.17am, so it was far too early to arrive with a bottle of wine as a gift. I improvised by grabbing a pack of bacon that I had been thinking about for some time. Upon arrival, my suggestion of a bacon sandwich was greeted with approval. I wandered off to the kitchen to do my thing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lasagne Sandwich Recipe (EASY!)</title>
      <link>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/lasagne-sandwich/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2012 12:47:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/lasagne-sandwich/</guid>
      <description>[caption id=&amp;quot;&amp;quot; align=&amp;ldquo;alignright&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;ldquo;500&amp;rdquo;]Lasagne sandwich[/caption]
This is old news but&amp;hellip; Gutted you missed the lasagne sandwich Tesco were once selling? Really though? Did it seem like a good idea? The Guardian didn&amp;rsquo;t think so. Anyway.
The lasagne sandwich &amp;lsquo;recipe&amp;rsquo; The quick and dirty way to a delicious lasagne sandwich is this: 1. Get a bun 2. Cut bun 3. Flop entire lasagne wedge into bun 4. Close bun 5. Eat sandwichy goodness Okay, to make this badboy you have to have some lasagne to hand first.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Made Up TV Shows</title>
      <link>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/made-up-tv-shows/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Apr 2012 14:41:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/made-up-tv-shows/</guid>
      <description>What follows is a list of made up TV shows, because once all this rubbish is written down, it will leave my mind forever.
 ‘Tache in the Attic - game show where celebrities must be identified in the dark by touching their facial hair. Gran Designs - Kevin McCloud personally sponsors a family to live for a year in a house designed by a grandparent who knows nothing of architecture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Speed Up Your Samsung N145 Plus Netbook</title>
      <link>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/how-to-speed-up-your-samsung-n145-plus-netbook/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Apr 2012 14:22:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/how-to-speed-up-your-samsung-n145-plus-netbook/</guid>
      <description>[Edited 2020-05-15: Emerge Desktop&amp;rsquo;s website no longer exists so I linked to an archive.org backup] I&amp;rsquo;ve been using a Samsung N145 Plus netbook for a while now. Whilst I am happy with it in general, I do find that sometimes it slows down for no apparent reason. Here are a few tips to help speed up your machine that you might not have thought of.
Use the right web browser at the right time I find that Google Chrome starts quickest on the N145 Plus, so I use that if I quickly want to check email or look something up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senet, An Ancient Egyptian Board Game</title>
      <link>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/senet-egyptian-board-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2012 14:08:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/senet-egyptian-board-game/</guid>
      <description>What is Senet? [caption id=&amp;quot;&amp;quot; align=&amp;ldquo;alignright&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;ldquo;240&amp;rdquo;]Senet game at the British Museum[/caption] Senet (or &amp;ldquo;senat&amp;rdquo;) is (or was) an ancient Egyptian board game. It&amp;rsquo;s a bit like snakes and ladders, and a bit like backgammon. It&amp;rsquo;s easy to get into and doesn&amp;rsquo;t have too many rules either.
The Rules of Senet The rules of Senet are not definite &amp;ndash; they&amp;rsquo;ve never been discovered, so the best guess at how the game works comes from scholars who have examined the boards that have been found, the imagery found on them, and how the special squares (depecting stages on the journey to the Egyptian afterlife) might relate to the players&#39; progress.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Strip HTML Tags Online with zubrag.com</title>
      <link>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/strip-html-tags-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Mar 2012 20:55:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/strip-html-tags-online/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;re looking for a tool to strip HTML tags online, perhaps the one at zubrag.com can help. Bit of background: I update a website every week or so with a post based on a newsletter that comes in DOC format. I convert it to HTML to extract the images easily (they&amp;rsquo;re saved in a directory), then I upload them to Wordpress. What I&amp;rsquo;m left with is a bit horrible because Word does not clean up HTML before it renders it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anarchy in the UK</title>
      <link>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/anarchy-in-the-uk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2012 18:08:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/anarchy-in-the-uk/</guid>
      <description>&amp;hellip;starting with the seasonal ice cream vending industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Richmond Castle Panoramic Photo</title>
      <link>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/richmond-castle-photos-panoramic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2011 21:58:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/richmond-castle-photos-panoramic/</guid>
      <description>Not because I think the photo is any good, but rather because I wanted to link to Hugin which is an amazing bit of software for making panoramic photos by joining together smaller ones, I thought I would post this panoramic photo of Richmond Castle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Tasks Canvas</title>
      <link>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/google-tasks-canvas/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2011 07:46:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/google-tasks-canvas/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s true that the Google Tasks is nothing new but I&amp;rsquo;m using it more and more for noting down ad hoc lists of tasks and things that don&amp;rsquo;t need processing. The URL for the Google Tasks Canvas View (a more tablet friendly multi-pane version) is https://mail.google.com/tasks/canvas and you&amp;rsquo;ll need to be logged into a Google account for any Google Tasks functionality (it&amp;rsquo;s sort of part of Gmail). It&amp;rsquo;s very lightweight and not intended to be a replacement for Basecamp or Remember the Milk, but it does what it has to well, and as with any Google product there is always scope for development (for example they recently added an API which is very promising).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adwords: Segment By Conversion Type</title>
      <link>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/adwords-segment-by-conversion-type/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2011 11:50:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/adwords-segment-by-conversion-type/</guid>
      <description>You can now segment by conversion type in Adwords (now directly as part of the interface anyway). Previously I think these were only available as part of adding segments to a downloaded AdWords report. Not a lot of metrics showing up at the moment and it doesn&amp;rsquo;t seem to work with all accounts but a welcome additions to the segmentation available through the actual AdWords interface! To enable this go to the usual Dimensions tab, and where you would normally segment by time you can now see Conversion options as above.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#34;Could not connect to Evernote server&#34; fix</title>
      <link>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/could-not-connect-to-evernote-server-fix/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2011 22:52:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/could-not-connect-to-evernote-server-fix/</guid>
      <description>This is a problem I&amp;rsquo;ve only ever had on Windows 7 but I gather it can affect you on XP too. If Evernote says
 Synchronization failed, could not connect to Evernote server
 and you aren&amp;rsquo;t sure why because everything else seems to work on the internet, go to Tools menu, Options, then the General tab and then click on &amp;ldquo;Log folder&amp;rdquo;. If in recent logs you can see</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google&#39;s other Android USB Keychain</title>
      <link>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/googles-other-android-usb-keychain/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2011 22:44:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/googles-other-android-usb-keychain/</guid>
      <description>Not sure if this is that exciting but there was a post at Search Engine Roundtable about a Google USB stick in the shape of the Android, er, android. Obtained this similar one a few weeks back&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Evernote Mobile web interface for quick notetaking</title>
      <link>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/evernote-mobile-web-interface-for-quick-notetaking/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2011 11:52:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/evernote-mobile-web-interface-for-quick-notetaking/</guid>
      <description>[caption id=&amp;ldquo;attachment_145&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;ldquo;alignright&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;ldquo;214&amp;rdquo; caption=&amp;ldquo;Evernote Mobile interface could help save time when taking notes&amp;rdquo;][/caption] I&amp;rsquo;ve been using Evernote&amp;rsquo;s Mobile web interface (http://evernote.com/m/) to take notes quickly on desktop PCs. I find the full Evernote interface (desktop client or web) a too distracting if all I want to do is make some plain text notes without reviewing what&amp;rsquo;s already there. (NB: On Ubuntu I found Firefox gave me an XML error when visiting the mobile site, whereas Chrome worked fine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to use negative keywords in the Google Adwords Keyword Tool</title>
      <link>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/how-to-use-negative-keywords-in-the-google-adwords-keyword-tool/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2011 17:13:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/how-to-use-negative-keywords-in-the-google-adwords-keyword-tool/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m sure this is common knowledge, but it&amp;rsquo;s worth noting that whilst doing keyword research using Google&amp;rsquo;s external keyword tool you can use negative keywords like so:  This is useful if you want to refine your keyword list before exporting to CSV. Also, when you tick &amp;ldquo;only show ideas closely related to my search terms&amp;rdquo; it tends to return ideas that are almost exactly related to your search terms, which can be too limiting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Convert wav to mp3 online with media.io</title>
      <link>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/convert-wav-to-mp3-online-with-media-io/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2011 19:15:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/convert-wav-to-mp3-online-with-media-io/</guid>
      <description>A few days ago I needed to convert a short wav file to mp3 format. I wanted to email a recording to a few friends, and the wav filecame in around 15mb, so I figured converting to mp3 would be a good idea, to save time and bandwidth (especially since what I was sending was so trivial that quality didn&amp;rsquo;t matter). I didn&amp;rsquo;t want to install any extra software on my work PC (although Audacity is always installed at home!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to hide your Posterous profile</title>
      <link>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/how-to-hide-your-posterous-profile/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2010 11:59:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/how-to-hide-your-posterous-profile/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m not claiming this makes your Posterous anonymous at all, but if you would like to hide your profile information from being displayed on your Posterous site/blog/whatever:
 Go to &amp;ldquo;Manage&amp;rdquo; Go to &amp;ldquo;Theme my site&amp;rdquo; Click on &amp;ldquo;Advanced&amp;rdquo; and name your new template Expand the editor using the link on the right Remove everything from and including &amp;lt;section id=&amp;ldquo;profile&amp;rdquo;&amp;gt; up to and including the relevant occurrence of  Repeat for other sections if you want to remove contributor lists etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Technika TKNM110 nano wireless optical mouse driver issue</title>
      <link>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/technika-tknm110-nano-wireless-optical-mouse-driver-issue/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2010 15:39:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/technika-tknm110-nano-wireless-optical-mouse-driver-issue/</guid>
      <description>Putting this out there in the hope that it helps someone else who&amp;rsquo;s had issues with this mouse (which is otherwise pretty comfy and good value IMO). I bought it from Tesco (who I think own the Technika brand, but seemingly don&amp;rsquo;t want to support it very well). It wouldn&amp;rsquo;t install cleanly in Vista, claiming at the end of the driver install process that the device was unknown. From what I gather this is a general Vista USB mouse issue, but this was where I found the solution for my own problem: http://channel9.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>XML Schema for Todo/Task lists?</title>
      <link>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/xml-todo-list-task-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2010 19:02:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/xml-todo-list-task-list/</guid>
      <description>[Edit: added a question mark to the end of the post title, in case anyone thinks I&amp;rsquo;ve written something formal&amp;hellip; ideally someone else will because I don&amp;rsquo;t have anything like the know-how :-) ] Okay, forgive me if I&amp;rsquo;ve got that terminology all wrong, but in practical terms I&amp;rsquo;m out of my depth here. I&amp;rsquo;m probably going over very old ground, but has anyone come up with an XML open standard/schema for declaring items on a task list or todo list (or multiple lists)?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Wildhearts at Exeter Phoenix</title>
      <link>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/the-wildhearts-live-at-exeter-phoenix/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2009 00:02:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/the-wildhearts-live-at-exeter-phoenix/</guid>
      <description>Sorting through the digital detritus ready for a minimalist 2010, I found these colourful but amateurish mobile snaps of The Wildhearts at Exeter Phoenix on 22nd September 2009. See Wildhearts photos!

Wildhearts @ Exeter Phoenix</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Bit Better RTM tweak - hide empty lists in Remember the Milk</title>
      <link>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/a-bit-better-rtm-tweak-hide-empty-lists-in-remember-the-milk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Nov 2009 16:37:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/a-bit-better-rtm-tweak-hide-empty-lists-in-remember-the-milk/</guid>
      <description>I use Remember the Milk to keep track of the following:
 &amp;ldquo;project-less&amp;rdquo; tasks that do not require a structure around them tasks that repeat (not one of the strong points of Basecamp et al) tasks that need to be worked on at more specific times  For personal, non-collaborative tasks, I think RTM is pretty clever. There&amp;rsquo;s no respite though. It gives you quick access to empty lists so you can add things to them easily.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First impressions: Basecamp vs TeamworkPM vs ProjectPier</title>
      <link>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/basecamp-alternatives/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2009 21:30:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/basecamp-alternatives/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;ve been using Basecamp at work, it&amp;rsquo;s really good. It&amp;rsquo;s easy enough to note down everything you need to whilst focusing on doing rather than delegating, deferring, due dates etc. In fact there aren&amp;rsquo;t really any due dates (unless you link a task to a milestone, and unless I&amp;rsquo;ve missed something). This is good if you are feeling proactive, because you will find something to do. It&amp;rsquo;s bad if there are 50 odd tasks lying around, and you don&amp;rsquo;t know which to do first.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2009 20:55:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/contact/</guid>
      <description>Email is my initials @ this domain. Twitter is fine too: https://www.twitter.com/tomfbush</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Tom Bush</title>
      <link>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/about-tom-bush/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2009 20:44:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/about-tom-bush/</guid>
      <description>About me There are a number of people called Tom Bush out there. So as to distinguish myself from the others, I have written this short page detailing parts of my life to date. I am (in varying measures) a guitar-playing, internet marketing, Linux-using friendly sort of a chap.
Employment I have a strong background in biddable media, but am also experienced with SEO, content, analytics and turning business, market and competitor data into insightful and actionable next steps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2009 17:43:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/projects/</guid>
      <description> I&amp;rsquo;ve made a list of ways to save money that might be helpful Remove unused labels from Todoist &amp;ndash; short, badly written script that uses the Todoist API to check which labels your task use, and removes the others Inspired by GTD I made a very basic weekly review app to learn a bit about Angular that you can clone and customise  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>editorial analytics: what is it?</title>
      <link>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/editorial-analytics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/editorial-analytics/</guid>
      <description>blah blah blah</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
