<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Productivity on Tom Bush | Data Science | SEO | Web Analytics</title>
    <link>/tags/productivity/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Productivity on Tom Bush | Data Science | SEO | Web Analytics</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2017 20:15:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/productivity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Review Checklist App</title>
      <link>/posts/weekly-review-checklist-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2017 20:15:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/weekly-review-checklist-app/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been toying with the idea of creating an app that helps with a weekly review for a while. I first came across the idea when reading about Getting Things Done and the massive list of &amp;lsquo;triggers&amp;rsquo; that comes with that. To be honest I found it a bit daunting and didn&amp;rsquo;t need to check all those things every week. So, in my own simple, trivial way I&amp;rsquo;ve written what is essentially just a web page with a list on it, except that the list updates a progress bar and nicely removes things from focus when they are complete.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Year&#39;s Resolutions 2013: The Year of Aiming Low and Planning Ahead</title>
      <link>/posts/new-years-resolutions-2013/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2012 18:30:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/new-years-resolutions-2013/</guid>
      <description>Why I can&amp;rsquo;t keep a resolution I make on New Year&amp;rsquo;s Eve Yes yes, I know it&amp;rsquo;s a bit early to be posting my New Year&amp;rsquo;s resolutions for 2013, but every December 31st I decide that I should probably choose to give up something, start doing something, start giving up something or whatever, and I never stick to it because:
 It&amp;rsquo;s not a realistic goal I&amp;rsquo;m clearly not that bothered if I don&amp;rsquo;t want to change it all year round It&amp;rsquo;s usually something vague that allows me to interpret my own rule to the point that the only thing I achieve is outwitting myself  With these points in mind, I have decided to make a list of multiple easy resolutions that will result in an overall net happiness increase, either because they save me money, remove clutter from my head or my room, or may have some kind of other health impact.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Tasks Canvas</title>
      <link>/posts/google-tasks-canvas/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2011 07:46:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/google-tasks-canvas/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s true that the Google Tasks is nothing new but I&amp;rsquo;m using it more and more for noting down ad hoc lists of tasks and things that don&amp;rsquo;t need processing. The URL for the Google Tasks Canvas View (a more tablet friendly multi-pane version) is https://mail.google.com/tasks/canvas and you&amp;rsquo;ll need to be logged into a Google account for any Google Tasks functionality (it&amp;rsquo;s sort of part of Gmail). It&amp;rsquo;s very lightweight and not intended to be a replacement for Basecamp or Remember the Milk, but it does what it has to well, and as with any Google product there is always scope for development (for example they recently added an API which is very promising).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Evernote Mobile web interface for quick notetaking</title>
      <link>/posts/evernote-mobile-web-interface-for-quick-notetaking/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2011 11:52:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/evernote-mobile-web-interface-for-quick-notetaking/</guid>
      <description>[caption id=&amp;ldquo;attachment_145&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;ldquo;alignright&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;ldquo;214&amp;rdquo; caption=&amp;ldquo;Evernote Mobile interface could help save time when taking notes&amp;rdquo;][/caption] I&amp;rsquo;ve been using Evernote&amp;rsquo;s Mobile web interface (http://evernote.com/m/) to take notes quickly on desktop PCs. I find the full Evernote interface (desktop client or web) a too distracting if all I want to do is make some plain text notes without reviewing what&amp;rsquo;s already there. (NB: On Ubuntu I found Firefox gave me an XML error when visiting the mobile site, whereas Chrome worked fine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>XML Schema for Todo/Task lists?</title>
      <link>/posts/xml-todo-list-task-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2010 19:02:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/xml-todo-list-task-list/</guid>
      <description>[Edit: added a question mark to the end of the post title, in case anyone thinks I&amp;rsquo;ve written something formal&amp;hellip; ideally someone else will because I don&amp;rsquo;t have anything like the know-how :-) ] Okay, forgive me if I&amp;rsquo;ve got that terminology all wrong, but in practical terms I&amp;rsquo;m out of my depth here. I&amp;rsquo;m probably going over very old ground, but has anyone come up with an XML open standard/schema for declaring items on a task list or todo list (or multiple lists)?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Bit Better RTM tweak - hide empty lists in Remember the Milk</title>
      <link>/posts/a-bit-better-rtm-tweak-hide-empty-lists-in-remember-the-milk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Nov 2009 16:37:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/a-bit-better-rtm-tweak-hide-empty-lists-in-remember-the-milk/</guid>
      <description>I use Remember the Milk to keep track of the following:
 &amp;ldquo;project-less&amp;rdquo; tasks that do not require a structure around them tasks that repeat (not one of the strong points of Basecamp et al) tasks that need to be worked on at more specific times  For personal, non-collaborative tasks, I think RTM is pretty clever. There&amp;rsquo;s no respite though. It gives you quick access to empty lists so you can add things to them easily.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First impressions: Basecamp vs TeamworkPM vs ProjectPier</title>
      <link>/posts/basecamp-alternatives/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2009 21:30:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/basecamp-alternatives/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;ve been using Basecamp at work, it&amp;rsquo;s really good. It&amp;rsquo;s easy enough to note down everything you need to whilst focusing on doing rather than delegating, deferring, due dates etc. In fact there aren&amp;rsquo;t really any due dates (unless you link a task to a milestone, and unless I&amp;rsquo;ve missed something). This is good if you are feeling proactive, because you will find something to do. It&amp;rsquo;s bad if there are 50 odd tasks lying around, and you don&amp;rsquo;t know which to do first.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
