<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>PPC on Tom Bush | Data Science/SEO</title><link>https://tomfbush.github.io/tags/ppc/</link><description>Recent content in PPC on Tom Bush | Data Science/SEO</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-gb</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2014 17:22:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tomfbush.github.io/tags/ppc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Biddable Media: Will All Advertising One Day Be Biddable?</title><link>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/biddable-media-will-advertising-space-one-day-biddable/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2014 17:22:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/biddable-media-will-advertising-space-one-day-biddable/</guid><description>Introduction to biddable media Behind Google&amp;rsquo;s huge advertising revenue, behind those annoying banners you see all over the web, behind the skippable ads before YouTube videos is the phenomenon of real-time bidding (RTB). This is a method of buying advertising space that, rather than arranging it in advance via a tenancy or reservation buy (i.e. money up front at an agreed price), relies on an auction taking place usually at lightning speed, between interested parties.</description></item><item><title>Adwords: Segment By Conversion Type</title><link>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/adwords-segment-by-conversion-type/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2011 11:50:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/adwords-segment-by-conversion-type/</guid><description>You can now segment by conversion type in Adwords (now directly as part of the interface anyway). Previously I think these were only available as part of adding segments to a downloaded AdWords report. Not a lot of metrics showing up at the moment and it doesn&amp;rsquo;t seem to work with all accounts but a welcome additions to the segmentation available through the actual AdWords interface! To enable this go to the usual Dimensions tab, and where you would normally segment by time you can now see Conversion options as above.</description></item><item><title>How to use negative keywords in the Google Adwords Keyword Tool</title><link>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/how-to-use-negative-keywords-in-the-google-adwords-keyword-tool/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2011 17:13:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tomfbush.github.io/posts/how-to-use-negative-keywords-in-the-google-adwords-keyword-tool/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m sure this is common knowledge, but it&amp;rsquo;s worth noting that whilst doing keyword research using Google&amp;rsquo;s external keyword tool you can use negative keywords like so: This is useful if you want to refine your keyword list before exporting to CSV. Also, when you tick &amp;ldquo;only show ideas closely related to my search terms&amp;rdquo; it tends to return ideas that are almost exactly related to your search terms, which can be too limiting.</description></item></channel></rss>