<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>fixes on Tom Bush | Data Science | SEO | Web Analytics</title>
    <link>/tags/fixes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in fixes on Tom Bush | Data Science | SEO | Web Analytics</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2014 21:09:02 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/fixes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>bbLean flickering with Chrome/Firefox/other: FIX</title>
      <link>/posts/bblean-flickering-chrome-firefox-titlebar/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2014 21:09:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/bblean-flickering-chrome-firefox-titlebar/</guid>
      <description>I just loaded up bbLean as a way of speeding up my old Win7 laptop, only to discover that Google Chrome (the app I use the most) was flickering really badly because it has its own skin, and bbLean was trying to apply its own titlebar too. I would have just commented on Nimret&amp;rsquo;s blog to say thanks, but it seems that comments are turned off. I decided to post thanks and the method here instead (but you can read the original here).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Windows Update: Same Updates Over And Over Again (FIX)</title>
      <link>/posts/windows-update-same-updates-over-and-over-again-fix/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2012 20:25:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/windows-update-same-updates-over-and-over-again-fix/</guid>
      <description>[caption id=&amp;ldquo;attachment_250&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;ldquo;alignright&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;ldquo;199&amp;rdquo;] If Windows Update Failed One More Time My Laptop Would Look Like This (I Don&amp;rsquo;t Know Who That Girl Is Though)[/caption] There was me thinking that the Windows Update mechanism was designed to streamline updates to the operating system, eliminating the need to go to a website to download fixes and patches. Ha ha ha. Without realising it, I&amp;rsquo;ve been repeatedly shutting down to install the same Windows Updates on Vista for the past 2 weeks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#34;Could not connect to Evernote server&#34; fix</title>
      <link>/posts/could-not-connect-to-evernote-server-fix/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2011 22:52:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/could-not-connect-to-evernote-server-fix/</guid>
      <description>This is a problem I&amp;rsquo;ve only ever had on Windows 7 but I gather it can affect you on XP too. If Evernote says
 Synchronization failed, could not connect to Evernote server
 and you aren&amp;rsquo;t sure why because everything else seems to work on the internet, go to Tools menu, Options, then the General tab and then click on &amp;ldquo;Log folder&amp;rdquo;. If in recent logs you can see</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
